myfourmonkeys.com 2014-05-26

# Privacy Policy

The privacy of visitors to My Four Monkeys is important. The following is information on the types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit our sites, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Children Under the Age of 13**

We do not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information from persons under 13 years of age, and this website is not directed to persons under 13. Children under 13 years of age are not eligible for contests or giveaways on this site. If we learn that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on My Four Monkeys without verified parental consent, we will take the appropriate steps to delete the information.

**Information We Collect**

A. Information Submitted by a User

My Four Monkeys does not require registration to use the site. However, we collect personal information when you post a comment or enter a giveaway or contest. That information may include: Name or alias, email address, IP address, and in the case of contest winners, mailing address.

If you subscribe to My Four Monkeys via email, your email address will also be recorded by our FeedBiurner service. We do not share our mailing list with any entities and subscribers may opt out at any time.

B. Non-submitted Information Collected

My Four Monkeys may also collect non-personal information not associated with your identity to improve the site. This information includes your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), You country, city, or state, the browser you used to visit, the time you visited, and which pages you viewed.

C. Cookies and Web Beacons

We do not use cookies to store information about visitors to our sites. However, we use third party advertisements to support the sites. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our sites, which will also send the advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, or whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for targeting purposes to help show appropriate ads to the visitor. For example, these companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

At this time, My Four Monkeys is not participating in any affiliate programs, but if we so choose to in the future, some advertisers might also use cookies to track purchases made in order to pay our site a commission for sales made through affiliate links on our site. We may have access to the time and date of purchase, the merchant, the amount of sale, products purchased, and in some cases general location of the purchaser, but we do not have access to the name, mailing address, phone number, email address, or other personal identifying information of the user.

You can also chose to disable or selectively turn off cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with websites. For example, entirely blocking cookies can cause the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**How We Use Your Information**

My Four Monkeys uses your Internet Protocol (IP) address to help diagnose problems with our computer server, and to administer our web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you, and to gather broad demographic data. Your IP address contains no personal information about you. For example, it does not include your name, email, or mailing address.

We will not disclose any personal information about you without your prior consent, unless we have a belief that such action is necessary to: (i) comply with legal process or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of My Four Monkeys; (iii) protect the interests of users of our services other than you or any other person; or (iv) operate or conduct maintenance and repair of our services or equipment as authorized by law.

We do not sell or rent personal information about users to any third parties.

If you voluntarily disclose personal information in comments, that information might be collected and disseminated by third parties, and result in, among other things, unsolicited inquiries, messages, and offers from third parties. Although our comment form requires an email address, that is not shown to the public. Email address shown in the body of the comment, however, will be displayed. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in comments becomes public information and this third-party conduct is out of the control of My Four Monkeys. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

My Four Monkeys also contains links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

**Security**  
The personally identifiable information we collect is securely stored within our database, and we use standard, industry-wide practices for protecting your information. However, as effective as encryption technology is, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.

**Revisions and Amendments**  
If you have further privacy concerns please do not hesitate to ask us by contacting angie{at}myfourmonkeys.com. This Privacy Policy is effective as of June 24, 2011. This Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party. My Four Monkeys reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, modify, change or update this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update or modification on the sites. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting.
